m2p.com 2017-04-06

# 

We, m2p Entertainment Ltd., are the owner of the www.m2p.com website. We are committed to protecting your privacy and security. Any information you as user of the website provide is received, stored and managed by us in line with our Privacy and Security policies detailed below which is in line with European and UK regulation. By using our website you are agreeing to this policy and the use of cookies in line with the terms in this policy. 

_Privacy_

This Privacy Policy explains how m2p ('We/Us/Our') collect, store and use your personal data when you browse and use www.m2p.com (the 'Website'), and when you provide us with your personal data. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.  
By accessing, browsing or otherwise using the Website you confirm that you have read, understood and agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy, you must not use the Website. Our official company details are:  
m2p Entertainment ltd.  
41 King Street  
Midland House  
Luton  
Bedfordshire LU1 2DW

Our company is registered with Companies House under registration number 8615267.

We respect your right to privacy and are committed to maintaining it. We only collect, store and process your personal data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.  
You can surf our website without indicating your name or other personal data. We only save the name of you internet service provider, the webpage from which you visit our homepage and the name of the requested file (please see cookie info). This information is only analysed for statistical reasons and serves for the improvement of our offers. You as user remain completely anonymous. __  
Personal data is only collected if you enter it for the transaction between you and us or at the creation of a customer account or for the registration to our email newsletter. This data is only used for the settlement of the contract (processing payments) and the execution of your enquiries. After the complete settlement of the contract and the complete payment of the goods, your data is saved considering storage periods in terms of commercial and tax legislation. After expiration of this period the data is deleted.   
After the contract settlement, your email address is only used for the advertising purposes in form our newsletter if you had agreed to receive our electronic newsletter. You are able to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time via the link in the newsletter or you can inform us of this by sending an e-mail to info@m2p.com or calling our Customer Service team. We will immediately delete your email address after receiving such notification.  
The personal details you provide when registering with us a client can be viewed and altered at anytime by you, in the ‘My Account’ section of the website.  
We only share your information in these circumstances: with agents (including credit reference agencies, credit card clearing agencies transport/logistics companies and our third party customer services provider), if and when our company is ever sold or purchased by another company, or with outside research agencies for research about our own goods and services. We will never pass your data on to a third party for marketing purposes.   
If you choose or are provided with a password you must treat such information as confidential and you are responsible for any activities that occur under your account.  We shall not be liable for any loss or damage which may arise as a result of any failure by you to keep your password or other account information confidential.  
_Data transfer internationally_ __  
Information we collect maybe stored and processed in and moved between any of the countries we operate in. We will comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 in respect of any such transfers. Please be aware that such countries which are outside of EEA may not have the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, however our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy.   
_Cookies_  
**What are cookies?**  
‘Cookies’ are small text files that are stored on your computer. Our online shops use cookies to improve and to secure our internet presence - for example to increase the navigation on our platform. Furthermore, cookies help us to analyse the frequency of our webpage views and the general navigation. Please note that some of these cookies are transmitted from our server to your system. In most cases these cookies are so called "Session -Cookies". Session cookies are deleted automatically from your hard-disk after your visit of our shops. Other cookies remain on your computer and allow us to recognize your computer during your next visit (so-called ‘persistent’ cookies). These cookies allow us to welcome you with your username and spare you retyping of your password and filling out forms with your data for subsequent orders.  
**Are cookies safe?**   
Yes. The information stored in cookies is safe and anonymous. They do not contain any information which could personally identify you and your account security is never compromised. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). For a video about cookies visit [www.google.co.uk/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies](http://www.google.co.uk/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies).

The table below outlines the cookies we use

**Name(s)** | 

**Purpose**

| 

**Cookie Length**  
  
---|---|---  
  
_t24g_session 

| 

Stores the User session ID of the current User 

| 

User session  
  
User_credentials 

| 

Used for easy Log-in, remember me function 

| 

10 Days  
  
Payment_method 

| 

Used to store preferred payment method only, no User data will be safed 

| 

User session  
  
twixJS 

| 

Stores the configuration of the website 

| 

1 year  
  
t24g_affiliate_id 

| 

Used to identify affiliate partner needs 

| 

1 month  
  
__UTMA 

| 

Used by google analytics 

| 

2 years  
  
__UTMB 

| 

Used by google analytics 

| 

1hr  
  
__UTMC 

| 

Used by google analytics 

| 

User session  
  
__UTMZ 

| 

Used by google analytics 

| 

180 Days  
  
**_Your consent_**  
M2p uses cookies to ensure that we provide the best possible standard of service to our online customers. However, as part of our privacy and security policy, we require your consent to use them.  
We currently have an “implied consent” policy in place. This means that we will assume by your continued use of our website that you are happy for us to use cookies unless you take certain steps to opt out of using the same.   
Should you not consent to the use of cookies on the site please see the section below for more information.   
**Can I turn off cookies?**   
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies or be notified each time a cookie is about to be used by modifying the settings in your browser. The majority of browsers will allow the user to alter the settings used for cookies. The help menu on your browser will have further details.   
Please remember that turning cookies off will restrict your access to our website. If you have your browser set to disable all cookies then you may not be able to access parts of the www.de.m2p.com website. If your browser is set to prompt you when cookies are being used, you will have to answer ‘yes’ when prompted to gain full access.

_Access to your Information_  
You have the right to view and correct the data we hold on you.   
You also have the right to stop the collection of this information on you and delete any information we hold on you. If you have any further questions concerning the collection, execution or usage of your personal data, do not hesitate to contact us. The same applies for correction desires concerning your personal data and for revocation of agreed consents. For our contact details see the imprint page.   
_Security_  
At m2p we take your online security very seriously. Full details of how we protect the information you provide us are given below. __  
Our website uses the latest technologies to provide a safe, secure site for electronic commerce transactions, including secure socket layer (SSL) technology for payment transactions. SSL is a method for establishing a link between one computer and another safe one. Banks also use these links for online banking. You will recognise an SSL link by the little padlock which appears on the lower right in the menu bar of your browser and at the address bar which begins with "https" instead of "http". In this case the "S" stands for "secure".    
E-mail correspondence is not a secure means of communication as it is a free format text and cannot be encrypted.  Although we use advanced security measures to protect your information against loss, misuse and alterations, because of the nature of the internet we cannot guarantee the security of your information provided to us over the internet and cannot be held responsible for this. ".   
_Your Consent_  
By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes. __

Stand 18.03.2014
